

WEB DEVELOPER | FULL STACK EDUCATION

Looking to make an impact developing ideas on apps and websites on a smart motivated team. Ideal environment would provide opportunities for growth, support achievement, developing new skills, collaboration and hard work.

- *3+ years experience developing and managing multiple HTML and CSS Front-End websites.
- *Earned Full Stack Ruby on Rails, Mongodb, Angular, Node, Express and Front-End HTML/CSS certificates.
- *Developed tool for less technical staff to resolve most support issues at AT&T that still saves \$ today.
- *Social media wizard and early adopter of cross platform promotion and growth hacker marketing.

Web Development

jQuery

Mention"

• Emirates Travel

"Best Tweets"

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

 HTML5 Github Code Repository - github.com/readysetrock CSS3 Open source code contributions, projects and snippets. Javascript

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer - Contractor Ajax

University of San Francisco 2016 - Present API

Designing and developing a front-end dashboard with the Tableau API linked to Languages Postgres DB on Tableau Server. JavaScript | HTML5 | CSS | ¡Query | Bootstrap |

 Javascript Tableau Server | Tableau API

 Ruby Instructor Volunteer

 Python Mission Bit | San Francisco 2015 - 2016

Kids After School Coding Program providing project advice and teaching kids to code. **Databases**

Independent Contractor Sqlite

Getaround, Fitbit, Sol Republic, and Zynga | San Francisco 2012 - 2015 MongoDB These roles were not primarily technical but did rely on a number of multi-Servers disciplinary skills. Each opportunity exposed me to an app or start-up idea that Apache

inspired me on some level. This exposure re-sparked interest in web development • Node.js

and led to the decision to level up my coding skills.

Frameworks Event Operations, Front-End Developer, Social Media Manager

ReadySetRock! | San Francisco 2006 - 2012 Angular. js

A typical day was never typical, and one day never looked like the next. Out of Express necessity grew websites, blogs, and social media skills. Designed and managed Socket.io entertainment website. Developed social media growth hacking marketing campaigns Rails

linking multiple platforms (websites, WordPress, Twitter, Facebook, Instagram,

 Bootstrap Google) to promote artists and events.

Hackathons 2015 Operations Manager, Project Manager, Support Engineer I & II

AT&T Internet Services | San Francisco 2000 - 2006 Lincoln Labs

As a function of the role, created and managed internal and external static HTML "Honorable

websites. Created tools to clear a backlog of 35,000 customer care emails. Developed and delivered technical training program to AT&T outsource centers. Award winning Tier 2 technical network support engineer, earning customer high praise and 2 AT&T

customer service awards.

EDUCATION | PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Coding Dojo - Full Stack Engineer - 14 week immersive bootcamp - San Jose, December 2015

Earned Certificates Double Blackbelt | Ruby on Rails | MEAN Stack Mongodb, Express, Angular, Node

Hack Reactor - Front-End Developer - 4 week course - San Francisco, August 2015

Javascript, HTML5, jQuery, CSS, JSON, Bootstrap

Oklahoma State University - Bachelor of Science - Stillwater, July 1991

Recreation, Administration and Management

Walt Disney College Program Internship - Disney University Graduate

Completed 25 Graduate School hours: Data Science, International Marketing, Experiential Education